kovideo.net 2013-11-26

# 

At kovideo.net, we are committed to respecting people’s privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our website. In order to do so, we may gather certain personal information about you. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our website. By using kovideo.net, you consent to the collection and use of your information by KOvideo as described in this Policy, and you signify your agreement to the KOvideo Privacy Policy.

**What information does KOvideo collect?**  
When you visit kovideo.net, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited and any feedback from our visitors. We then aggregate this information with other pieces of information to improve our site and make your experience on the site as valuable and efficient as possible.  
When you register for the website, we collect personal information such as name, age, address, phone and email in order to set up your account.   
In addition to the information we collect upon your initial registration with kovideo.net, we may ask you for personal information at other times, including, but not limited to, when you enter promotions or contests, and when you respond to a survey.  
Upon cancelling your KOvideo account, you have the right to request deletion of your account information, subject to our need to keep appropriate archives for our business operations. 

**What do we do with the information we collect?**  
1\. It is used to set up and maintain your kovideo.net account. If you provide us with your mobile phone information, we may use such information to communicate with you regarding kovideo.net by SMS, MMS, text message or other electronic means to a mobile device.  
2\. Your phone number may be used in the event that our customer service representatives need to contact you and cannot reach you by email.  
3\. Your personal information will never be sold to any other website owner or merchant. We hate junk mail as much as you. This is why we will only send you email about items that we feel you should know about. This includes special promotional items that KOvideo endorses, membership changes, terms and conditions changes, Holiday cards, friend updates and the latest happenings on kovideo.net. When we send you emails that include a link to the website, that link may contain an alphanumeric identifier that allows us to identify the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our content for that individual. 

**Email Opt-out**  
Users who no longer wish to receive our email updates or other notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable email or by logging-in and changing their account settings.

**With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?**  
KOvideo does not sell, rent, or trade any personally identifying information with others. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s). If we intend to share such information, you will be notified prior to the collection of that information. If you do not want your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion or contest.  
We may also share aggregate user information in a non-personally identifiable manner with advertisers and other third parties in order to present to users more targeted advertising, products and services.  
We may contract with third parties to conduct research and marketing on our behalf. Such third parties will be fully bound by an obligation of confidentiality to KOvideo and may not use any personally-identifiable information provided by us other than as expressly instructed by us and in strict compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

**What information do parties other than KOvideo collect?**  
Some entities that have links on our site may collect personally identifying information about you when you access or utilize those links. KOvideo does not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.  
It is important to note that those entities may not follow the same privacy policies as KOvideo. For instance, if you click on an advertisement on kovideo.net, you may be taken away from kovideo.net to an entirely different site. These links can also be from advertisers, content providers and/or partners who may use kovideo.net’s logo and/or style as a result of a co-branding agreement yet they may still not follow the same privacy policies as KOvideo. 

**What are “cookies” and “web beacons” and how do we use them?**  
Our site may use “cookies” and “web beacons” to speed navigation, keep track of items, and provide you with custom-tailored services. A “web beacon” is an embedded GIF file that specifically helps us track whether you have viewed a specific piece of content. We also use “cookies” to remember information you gave us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the site. By showing us how and when visitors use the site, “cookies” and “web beacons” help us see which site areas and content are popular and which are not. We also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to any sponsors. Some advertisers or websites that have links on our site may also use their own “cookies.”  
Most browsers are initially set to accept “cookies.” If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse “cookies.” You will not be able to use our service if you turn off the “cookies” option. Also you may wish to opt-out of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and updating your cookie options. Learn more about cookies [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/learn_more.asp). 

**Security**  
Our member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. In addition, we use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff.  
However, please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of our member information at any time. 

**Business transitions**  
In the event KOvideo goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

**Cooperation with law enforcement; fraud protection**  
KOvideo fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to disclose information about members who we believe are in violation of applicable laws or regulations, or as required to respond to a subpoena, court orders or other legal process requiring such disclosure. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful and to exchange information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy** Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used or collected. From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy and will notify you of those changes by email or post a notice on the kovideo.net website. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use kovideo.net after such changes have been first posted. Please note that if you opt out of receiving legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of kovideo.net, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes. 

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising** We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at http://www.networkadvertising.org. To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices. 

**Some of our Partners Privacy Policies** We strongly ecourage you to review also our partners advertising policies since those also impact your privacy on our site.  

  * [SourceKnowledge](http://sourceknowledge.com/privacy.php) / [ProvenPixel](http://provenpixel.com/privacy.html)

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to us by using the [contact page](http://www.kovideo.net/contact.html) or by directly emailing [contact@kovideo.net](mailto:contact@kovideo.net).
